=Stealing Heart=
= سرقة القلب =
=Episode 4= (His Heart is All Over the Place)
= الحلقة 4 = (قلبه في كل مكان)
Who's out there?
من هناك؟
Show yourself.
أظهر نفسك.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
Chuning,
التغيير
should I kill him?
هل يجب أن أقتله؟
Mr. Gao is Lu Siyan's uncle.
السيد غاو هو عم لو سيان.
He must have complicated connections to the Wenrou Lounge.
يجب أن يكون لديه صلات معقدة مع صالة وينرو.
If he tells Lu Siyan,
T T Tands Lu Siyan ،
we're done for.
لقد انتهينا من أجل.
I'm not his uncle.
أنا لست عمه.
Back then, your great-grandfather brought me into the family just to ward off bad luck.
في ذلك الوقت ، جلبني جدك إلى العائلة فقط لدرء الحظ السيئ.
But not long after,
ولكن لم يمض وقت طويل ،
your father was born.
ولد والدك.
I didn't even change my surname. I'm still Gao.
لم أغير حتى لقبي. ما زلت قاو.
To Lu Siyan,
إلى لو سيان ،
the three of us are the same.
الثلاثة منا هي نفسها.
We are outsiders.
نحن الغرباء.
Mochen,
موشن ،
Mr. Gao has been supporting
السيد غاو كان يدعم
the Foundling Home all these years.
المنزل الإقليمي كل هذه السنوات.
I don't wish to be ungrateful.
لا أرغب في أن أكون غير مفيد.
But just in case,
ولكن فقط في حالة ،
we should tie him up.
يجب أن نربطه.
Mr. Gao,
السيد غاو ،
you'll have to stay here for a few days.
سيكون عليك البقاء هنا لبضعة أيام.
We'll figure out what to do with you
سنكتشف ماذا نفعل معك
once we're done with Lu Siyan.
بمجرد الانتهاء من لو سيان.
(Lu Siyan,)
(لو سيان ،)
(it's time to settle the score)
(حان الوقت لتسوية النتيجة)
(between us.)
(بيننا)
(Lu Residence)
(Lu Residence)
Siyan,
الشراء ،
do you know Wenrou Lounge?
هل تعرف صالة وينرو؟
(Mochen,)
(موشن ،)
(lure Lu Siyan out of the city with Wenrou Lounge.)
(إغراء لو سيان خارج المدينة مع صالة وينرو.)
(To keep his secret there, he'll definitely show up.)
(للحفاظ على سره هناك ، سوف يظهر بالتأكيد.)
Chuning found out the secret in Wenrou Lounge.
اكتشف تشونينج السر في صالة وينرو.
She arranged to meet the owner
رتبت لمقابلة المالك
at an abandoned warehouse in the western suburbs.
في مستودع مهجور في الضواحي الغربية.
She left this morning
غادرت هذا الصباح
and hasn't come back.
ولم يعود.
I think something's happened to her.
أعتقد أن هناك شيئًا ما حدث لها.
I'll go with you.
سأذهب معك.
(Lu Siyan is skilled.)
(لو سيان ماهر.)
(Make sure you get him in one strike.)
(تأكد من الحصول عليه في ضربة واحدة.)
(Don't kill him.)
(لا تقتله.)
(I want him captured alive.)
(أريده القبض عليه على قيد الحياة.)
(What he owed Xiaorou,)
(ما يدين به شياوو ،)
(I'll make him pay)
(سأجعله يدفع)
(one by one.)
(واحد تلو الآخر.)
Lu Siyan.
لو سيان.
Like I said,
كما قلت ،
I'll make you suffer
سأجعلك تعاني
until you die in agony.
حتى تموت في العذاب.
(For the rest of your life,)
(لبقية حياتك ،)
(you'll be trapped in a dark dungeon,)
(سوف تكون محاصرة في زنزانة مظلمة ،)
(tortured and humiliated by me.)
(تعرض للتعذيب والإهانة من قبلي.)
Lin Chuning.
لين تشونينج.
Stop.
قف.
Or I'll kill her.
أو سأقتلها.
You're threatening me with him?
أنت تهددني به؟
It won't work.
لن يعمل.
You won't know
لن تعرف
until you try.
حتى تحاول.
You think I care about her?
هل تعتقد أنني أهتم بها؟
Kneel.
الركوع.
I said kneel!
قلت الركوع!
Lu Siyan,
لو سيان ،
I'll kill you.
سأقتلك.
You want to kill me?
تريد قتلي؟
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Lu Siyan.
لو سيان.
This whole setup
هذا الإعداد كله
was meant for me, right?
كان المقصود بالنسبة لي ، أليس كذلك؟
What were you planning to do to me?
ماذا كنت تخطط للقيام بي؟
Whatever you're thinking of doing now
كل ما تفكر في فعله الآن
is what I wanted to do.
هو ما أردت أن أفعله.
I wanted to save you,
أردت أن أنقذك ،
but you wanted to kill me.
لكنك أردت قتلي.
Drop your act.
إسقاط عملك.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Why was my pocket watch
لماذا كانت ساعة جيبي
with you?
معك؟
You...
أنت...
Just now...
الآن...
Yes.
نعم.
I'm asking you
أنا أسألك
why you had my pocket watch.
لماذا كان لديك ساعة الجيب الخاصة بي.
You know why.
أنت تعرف لماذا.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Lu Siyan,
لو سيان ،
you're a scumbag.
أنت scumbag.
Xiaorou and I
Xiaorou وأنا
won't let you off,
لن تتركك ،
even if we go to hell.
حتى لو ذهبنا إلى الجحيم.
Xiaorou?
Xiaorou؟
You gave her this pocket watch,
أعطيتها ساعة الجيب هذه ،
and you don't remember her name?
وأنت لا تتذكر اسمها؟
I only lost this a while ago.
لقد فقدت هذا منذ فترة فقط.
The Xiaorou you're talking about
Xiaorou الذي تتحدث عنه
is...
يكون...
Don't come near me.
لا تقترب مني.
Don't.
لا.
Scream.
يصرخ.
You screamed a lot.
صرخت كثيرا.
Why aren't you screaming now?
لماذا لا تصرخ الآن؟
Go on and scream.
استمر وصرخ.
Come on.
تعال.
I said scream.
قلت الصراخ.
Don't touch me.
لا تلمسني.
Please.
لو سمحت.
I'll be good.
سأكون جيدًا.
I beg of you.
أتوسل إليك.
Ah!
آه!
Wretched woman.
امرأة بائسة.
Let's see what I'll do to you.
دعونا نرى ما سأفعله لك.
Help!
يساعد!
Who are you?
من أنت؟
She's mine.
انها لي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You're here, Mr. Lu.
أنت هنا يا سيد لو.
Mr. Siyan,
السيد سيان ، ذلك ،
this is your second time here.
هذه هي المرة الثانية هنا.
You always sit and drink.
أنت دائما تجلس وتشرب.
Are you not happy with me?
هل أنت لست سعيدا معي؟
No, that's not it.
لا ، هذا ليس كذلك.
Come sit.
تعال اجلس.
I didn't do anything to her.
لم أفعل أي شيء لها.
I was afraid she'd misunderstand me,
كنت خائفة من أنها أسيء فهمي ،
so I paid the bartender regularly.
لذلك دفعت النادل بانتظام.
I never saw her again.
لم أرها مرة أخرى.
(Wait.)
(انتظر.)
(Xiaorou always wore her lucky charm.)
(Xiaorou ارتدت دائمًا سحرها المحظوظ.)
(If Lu Siyan really slept with her,)
(إذا كان لو سيان ينام معها حقًا ،)
(there's no way he wouldn't have noticed.)
(لا توجد طريقة لم يلاحظها.)
(Could I have misunderstood him?)
(هل كان بإمكاني فهمه؟)
(Was the child Xiaorou carried)
(هل كان الطفل Xiaorou يحمله)
(someone else's?)
(شخص آخر؟)
(But if she didn't sleep with him,)
(ولكن إذا لم تنام معه ،)
(why would she be so sure it was his?)
(لماذا ستكون متأكدة من أنها كانت؟)
What are you looking at?
ماذا تنظر؟
I wasn't looking at you.
لم أكن أنظر إليك.
So,
لذا،
you went to Wenrou Lounge
ذهبت إلى صالة وينرو
to look for Xiaorou?
للبحث عن Xiaorou؟
Why did you go there?
لماذا ذهبت إلى هناك؟
I want to find the one behind it all
أريد أن أجد الشخص الذي يقف وراء كل شيء
and stop more innocents from getting hurt.
ووقف المزيد من الأبرياء من التعرض للأذى.
Have you found them?
هل عثرت عليهم؟
Do you remember
هل تذكر
the ylang-ylang plant outside the study at Wenrou Lounge?
مصنع Ylang-ylang خارج الدراسة في Wenrou Lounge؟
Yes.
نعم.
That flower
تلك الزهرة
is hard to care for,
من الصعب رعاية ،
which makes it rare.
مما يجعلها نادرة.
One day,
يوم واحد،
I smelled ylang-ylang
شم رائحة يلانج إيلانغ
on my uncle,
على عمي ،
so I followed him.
لذلك تابعته.
Then,
ثم،
I ended up outside the study at Wenrou Lounge.
انتهى بي الأمر خارج الدراسة في صالة وينرو.
Mr. Gao?
السيد جاو؟
At first,
في البداية،
I thought this was dangerous.
اعتقدت أن هذا كان خطيرًا.
But now I feel like you have to know.
لكن الآن أشعر أن عليك أن تعرف.
If not,
إذا لم يكن كذلك ،
who knows you might come after me?
من يدري أنك قد تأتي بعدي؟
Hey.
يا.
Let's make peace here.
دعونا نجعل السلام هنا.
(No.)
(لا.)
(I can't trust anyone's word anymore.)
(لا أستطيع الوثوق بكلمة أي شخص بعد الآن.)
Then
ثم
why did you save me?
لماذا أنقذتني؟
Aren't you my sister?
أليست أختي
Why didn't you kill me?
لماذا لم تقتلني؟
You're my sister.
أنت أختي.
Didn't you say you don't want me
ألم تقل أنك لا تريدني
to be your sister?
لتكون أختك؟
Let me introduce myself again. Lu Siyan.
اسمحوا لي أن أقدم نفسي مرة أخرى. لو سيان.
Lu Chuning.
لو تشونينج.
Chief.
رئيس.
What have you done?
ماذا فعلت؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
(Sanshun, Shen Mochen's subordinate) Chief, it's too late. Let's leave.
(Sanshun ، رئيس Shen Mochen المرؤوس) ، فقد فات الأوان. دعنا نغادر.
Wait here.
انتظر هنا.
I'll deal with you later.
سأتعامل معك لاحقًا.
Chief,
رئيس،
the fire inside is too strong.
النار في الداخل قوية جدا.
Let the Lu siblings kill each other.
دع الأشقاء لو يقتلون بعضهم البعض.
You just need to marry Ms. Jing
تحتاج فقط إلى الزواج من السيدة جينغ
and enjoy everything that comes with it.
واستمتع بكل ما يأتي معه.
Chuning!
تغيير chunsing!
Chief.
رئيس.
Let go of me.
اتركي.
Chief,
رئيس،
there's something I need to report.
هناك شيء أحتاج إلى الإبلاغ عنه.
Sanshun,
سانشون ،
how long have you worked for me?
منذ متى وأنت تعمل من أجلي؟
Five years now.
خمس سنوات الآن.
Five years?
خمس سنوات؟
Yes, sir.
نعم يا سيدي.
Five years!
خمس سنوات!
Chief.
رئيس.
Do you know
هل تعرف
what it means to go beyond your role?
ماذا يعني أن تتجاوز دورك؟
Do you know what it means to overstep?
هل تعرف ماذا يعني تجاوز؟
Do you know what it means to follow orders?
هل تعرف ماذا يعني اتباع الأوامر؟
Why
لماذا
did you do that?
هل فعلت ذلك؟
Chief...
رئيس...
I did that for your own goodness.
فعلت ذلك من أجل الخير الخاص بك.
But are you aware that this could've gotten Chuning killed?
لكن هل أنت تدرك أن هذا قد يقتل؟
I...
أنا...
Enough.
كافٍ.
Don't explain.
لا تشرح.
Get out.
اخرج.
Yes, sir.
نعم يا سيدي.
Mr. Gao.
السيد غاو.
Why was Xiaorou's pocket watch
لماذا كانت ساعة جيب Xiaorou
with you?
معك؟
You...
أنت...
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
I've never seen this watch before.
لم أر هذه الساعة من قبل.
But
لكن
it was found in your room.
تم العثور عليه في غرفتك.
Your room at Wenrou Lounge.
غرفتك في صالة وينرو.
Mr. Siyan,
السيد سيان ، ذلك ،
is that you?
هل هذا أنت؟
please don't leave me.
من فضلك لا تتركني.
Mr. Siyan.
السيد هذا كل شيء.
Chuning,
التغيير
you really are a Lu through and through.
أنت حقا لو من خلال وعبر.
Just like your father and great-grandfather,
تماما مثل والدك وجدك ،
smart
ذكي
and cunning.
وكر.
So you admit it?
إذن أنت تعترف بذلك؟
I do.
أفعل.
But
لكن
what are you going to do about it?
ماذا ستفعل حيال ذلك؟
You burned
لقد أحرقت
the knockout incense, right?
البخور بالضربة القاضية ، أليس كذلك؟
You're trying to kill me?
هل تحاول قتلي؟
Yes.
نعم.
I want to kill you.
اريد قتلك.
Are you feeling
هل تشعر
itchy
مسبب للحكة
and numb?
وخدر؟
You...
أنت...
What's this happening?
ماذا يحدث هذا؟
This isn't knockout incense.
هذا ليس بالضربة القاضية.
This is the Ylang-ylang incense.
هذا هو البخور يلانغ إيلانغ.
The same incense
نفس البخور
I used on Xiaorou.
اعتدت على Xiaorou.
You good friends
أنتم أصدقاء جيدين
should share the same pleasure.
يجب مشاركة نفس المتعة.
Oh,
أوه،
right.
يمين.
One more thing.
شيء آخر.
This incense
هذا البخور
is my unique formula.
هي صيغة الفريدة الخاصة بي.
Xiaorou died because of you.
مات شياوو بسببك.
I'm going to kill you!
سأقتلك!
Kill me?
اقتلني؟
Let me tell you something.
دعني أخبرك بشيء.
What Xiaorou went through
ما مر به Xiaorou
wasn't on me.
لم يكن علي.
She just wasn't smart enough
لم تكن ذكية بما فيه الكفاية
and thought she could latch onto someone powerful.
واعتقدت أنها يمكن أن تمسك بشخص قوي.
Chuning,
التغيير
don't be like her.
لا تكن مثلها.
Be obedient,
كن مطيعا ،
and
و
I'll treat you well.
سأعاملك جيدًا.
Gao Yunfeng,
غاو يونفينج ،
you rot in hell!
أنت تتعفن في الجحيم!
Go to hell!
اذهب إلى الجحيم!
I like it when you're being so naughty.
يعجبني عندما تكون شقيًا جدًا.
- What are you trying to do? - Siyan. It's me.
- ماذا تحاول أن تفعل؟ - سيان. هذا أنا.
I'm your uncle.
أنا عمك.
Siyan,
الشراء ،
it's my fault.
إنه خطأي.
I won't do it again.
لن أفعل ذلك مرة أخرى.
Siyan.
الشراء.
Si...
و...
Siyan, look.
هذا كل شيء ، انظر.
Look at her.
انظر إليها.
You!
أنت!
Lin Chuning,
لين تشونينج ،
are you all right?
هل انت جميعا على حق؟
So hot.
حار جدا.
Lin Chuning.
لين تشونينج.
Chuning.
chunsing للقيام.
Wake up.
استيقظ.
Siyan.
الشراء.
I know you're not feeling well.
أعلم أنك لست على ما يرام.
I'll take you home.
سآخذك إلى المنزل.
♪Wanderers who found their way back♪
♪ المتجولون الذين وجدوا طريقهم إلى عودة ♪
♪Trade away their broken souls♪
♪ تداول أرواحهم المكسورة ♪
♪Boasting how painful their love once was♪
♪ يتفاخر بمدى مؤلم حبهم مرة واحدة ♪
(Lu Residence)
(Lu Residence)
♪My response is ambiguous♪
♪ ردي غامض ♪
♪Against my heart♪
♪ ضد قلبي ♪
♪With secrets I can't share♪
♪ مع أسرار لا أستطيع مشاركتها ♪
Feeling better now?
الشعور بتحسن الآن؟
♪How could I dare to lock my eyes♪
♪ كيف يمكنني أن أجرؤ على قفل عيني ♪
♪With yours♪
♪ مع لك ♪
So hot.
حار جدا.
I'll put you down.
سأضعك.
No.
لا.
♪You're the dark snow slowly arriving♪
♪ أنت الثلج المظلم الذي تصل ببطء ♪
♪Too high above the clouds♪
♪ مرتفع جدًا فوق الغيوم ♪
♪Unashamedly, I climb to reach♪
♪ بلا خجل ، أتسلق للوصول إلى ♪
It's hot.
الطقس حار.
♪Offering up my life with both hands♪
♪ تقديم حياتي بكلتا يديه ♪
Do you know who I am?
هل تعرف من أنا؟
Siyan.
الشراء.
♪Can hold on for a few more years♪
♪ يمكن أن تمسك لبضع سنوات أخرى ♪
♪But who can truly leave unscathed?♪
♪ ولكن من يستطيع أن يترك سالما حقًا؟ ♪
Lu Chuning.
لو تشونينج.
Chuning.
chunsing للقيام.
Don't do this.
لا تفعل هذا.
♪The sea of love, of sorrows, and of the crowd♪
♪ بحر الحب ، والأحزان ، والحشد ♪
Siyan.
الشراء.
♪I turn into white, pure snow♪
أتحول إلى ثلج أبيض نقي ♪
♪And vanish into ash♪
♪ ويختفي في الرماد ♪
♪Only in your gentle embrace can I find peace♪
♪ فقط في احتضانك اللطيف هل يمكنني أن أجد السلام ♪
Lin Chuning.
لين تشونينج.
♪I endured life's vicissitudes♪
لقد تحملت تقلبات الحياة ♪
I guess I owe you this.
أعتقد أنني مدين لك هذا.
No.
لا.
Go to sleep.
اذهب إلى النوم.
It's chilly at night.
انها باردة في الليل.
If you catch a cold,
إذا كنت تصاب بنزلة برد ،
don't expect me to look after you.
لا تتوقع مني أن أعتني بك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Sit.
يجلس.
If you don't mind,
إن لم يكن لديك مانع،
you can lean on my shoulder.
يمكنك أن تميل على كتفي.
It's nice to have a brother.
من الجيد أن يكون لديك أخ.
Having a sister is such a pain.
وجود أخت مثل هذا الألم.
You mean
تقصد
someone in the police station
شخص ما في مركز الشرطة
is in cahoots with Mr. Gao?
هل في Cahoots مع السيد Gao؟
Should we tell Mochen?
هل يجب أن نقول موشن؟
No.
لا.
I want to handle this myself.
أريد أن أتعامل مع هذا بنفسي.
As far as I'm concerned,
بقدر ما أشعر بالقلق ،
the person backing him in the police station
الشخص الذي يدعمه في مركز الشرطة
is Shen Mochen.
هو شين موتشن.
What makes you say so?
ما الذي يجعلك تقول ذلك؟
Shen Mochen
شين موشن
is shrewd
داهية
and ambitious.
وطموح.
He's been wanting
لقد كان يريد
to latch onto my sister
للمساءلة على أختي
and get a comfortable life.
والحصول على حياة مريحة.
My father bought him
اشترى والديه
this position as a chief.
هذا الموقف كرئيس.
You look down on him, don't you?
أنت تنظر إليه ، أليس كذلك؟
No, not just me.
لا ، ليس أنا فقط.
No one does.
لا أحد يفعل.
So,
لذا،
that day when I lured you out of the city
في ذلك اليوم عندما أغطيتك خارج المدينة
using Wenrou Lounge as an excuse,
باستخدام صالة وينرو كذريعة ،
you weren't afraid the plan might fail.
لم تكن خائفًا من فشل الخطة.
You were worried about me?
كنت قلقا علي؟
So, my sister,
لذا يا أختي ،
did you really mean to kill me
هل تقصد حقًا قتلي
because of Xiaorou?
بسبب Xiaorou؟
(Xianli Capital)
(Xianli Capital)
(Lu Siyan can't be trusted.)
(لو سيا يمكن أن يكون هذا هو التحالف.)
(Nor can Shen Mochen.)
(ولا يمكن شن موتشن.)
(The only person I can trust)
(الشخص الوحيد الذي يمكنني الوثوق به)
(is myself,)
(أنا نفسي ،)
(Caiyi, Wenrou Lounge dancer)
(Caiyi ، Wenrou Lounge Dancer)
Lin Chuning?
لين تشونينغ؟
Why'd you order her last time and not me?
لماذا تطلب لها آخر مرة وليس أنا؟
Come on. Open this.
تعال. افتح هذا.
You're so generous.
أنت سخية جدا.
How generous.
كيف سخية.
Stand right there.
قف هناك.
Are you new here?
هل أنت جديد هنا؟
Didn't I tell you to stay with me?
ألم أخبرك أن تبقى معي؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Mister,
مستر ،
this place is too crowded. I got lost.
هذا المكان مزدحم للغاية. لقد ضاعت.
I'll stay with you tonight.
سأبقى معك الليلة.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا
Why are you acting on your own again?
لماذا تتصرف بمفردك مرة أخرى؟
Childish.
صبيانية.
Mr. Gao killed Xiaorou.
السيد غاو قتل شياوو.
There's no way I'm letting him go.
لا توجد طريقة أتركه يذهب.
You're the matron of the Foundling Home.
أنت ماترون للمنزل.
If something happens to you, how would you face the other girls?
إذا حدث لك شيء ما ، فكيف تواجه الفتيات الأخريات؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll take good care of them.
سأعتني بهم جيدًا.
Mr. Gao
السيد غاو
must die.
يجب أن.
Come on, baby.
تعال يا حبيبي.
I'll make sure you have a good night tonight.
سوف أتأكد من أن لديك ليلة سعيدة الليلة.
♪Barging into the sea that bears your name♪
♪ المتخلل في البحر الذي يحمل اسمك ♪
♪Swimming to the end with loneliness♪
♪ السباحة حتى النهاية مع الوحدة ♪
♪Going against the current and over the reef traps♪
♪ الذهاب ضد التيار وعلى مصائد الشعاب المرجانية ♪
♪Clearing the fog just to get close to you♪
♪ مسح الضباب فقط للاقتراب منك ♪
♪Pushing away the gravel hidden beneath the seaweed♪
♪ دفع الحصى المخبأة تحت الأعشاب البحرية ♪
♪Wandering near your heart♪
♪ يتجول بالقرب من قلبك ♪
♪I imagined our encounter countless times♪
♪ تخيلت لقاءنا مرات لا تحصى ♪
♪So close, yet out of reach♪
♪ قريبة جدًا ، ولكن بعيد المنال ♪
♪Keeping all this lonely courage to myself♪
♪ الحفاظ على كل هذه الشجاعة الوحيدة لنفسي ♪
♪I was never part of your world♪
♪ لم أكن جزءًا من عالمك ♪
♪If your silhouette was etched upon the sea♪
♪ إذا كانت صورة ظلية محفورة على البحر ♪
♪The sky as your wedding dress♪
♪ السماء كما فستان الزفاف الخاص بك ♪
♪Turn me into a cloud♪
♪ تحويلني إلى سحابة ♪
♪Keep a sliver of the past♪
♪ احتفظ بشظية من الماضي ♪
♪If love is like an illusory bubble♪
♪ إذا كان الحب مثل فقاعة وهمية ♪
♪Together forever in my dreams♪
♪ معًا إلى الأبد في أحلامي ♪
♪I'd rest forever in your arms♪
♪ سأستريح إلى الأبد بين ذراعيك ♪
♪Barging into the sea that bears your name♪
♪ المتخلل في البحر الذي يحمل اسمك ♪
♪Swimming to the end with loneliness♪
♪ السباحة حتى النهاية مع الوحدة ♪
♪Going against the current and over the reef traps♪
♪ الذهاب ضد التيار وعلى مصائد الشعاب المرجانية ♪
♪Clearing the fog just to get close to you♪
♪ مسح الضباب فقط للاقتراب منك ♪
♪Returning to the land left bare by the receding sea♪
♪ العودة إلى الأرض تركت عارية من البحر المتساقط ♪
♪Withering like a fallen leaf♪
♪ يذبل مثل ورقة ساقطة ♪
♪The message in a bottle buried on the shore♪
♪ الرسالة الموجودة في زجاجة مدفونة على الشاطئ ♪
♪No one asked♪
♪ لم يطلب أحد ♪
♪All this lonely courage for myself♪
♪ كل هذه الشجاعة الوحيدة لنفسي ♪
♪I'm no longer part of your world♪
♪ لم أعد جزءًا من عالمك ♪
♪If your silhouette was etched upon the sea♪
♪ إذا كانت صورة ظلية محفورة على البحر ♪
♪The sky as your wedding dress♪
♪ السماء كما فستان الزفاف الخاص بك ♪
♪Turn me into a cloud♪
♪ تحويلني إلى سحابة ♪
♪Keep a sliver of the past♪
♪ احتفظ بشظية من الماضي ♪
♪If love is like an illusory bubble♪
♪ إذا كان الحب مثل فقاعة وهمية ♪
♪Together forever in my dreams♪
♪ معًا إلى الأبد في أحلامي ♪
♪I'd rest forever in your arms♪
♪ سأستريح إلى الأبد بين ذراعيك ♪
♪If the sea didn't wait for the evening breeze♪
♪ إذا لم ينتظر البحر نسيم المساء ♪
♪And swim with me to you♪
♪ والسباحة معي لك ♪
♪I'd become♪
♪ سأصبح ♪
♪A whale who forever keeps the sea company♪
♪ حوت يحتفظ بشركة البحر إلى الأبد
♪If love is like a night storm♪
♪ إذا كان الحب مثل عاصفة ليلية ♪
♪Unable to stop for a moment♪
♪ غير قادر على التوقف للحظة ♪
♪Let the wind scatter my traces♪
♪ دع الرياح تنتشر آثاري ♪